（戸崎優(とさきゆう)）
くっ…
（永井圭(ながいけい)）
うわあー！
The bosses are not happy, Tosaki.
（大臣）
社長たちが怒っているぞ 戸崎
What can I do... At this rate...
I might be disposed of...
（戸崎）
どうする？　このままでは
最悪 始末される
（銃声）
（ＳＰ）おっ…
Go ahead.
（オグラ･イクヤ）
構わんよ
この世に未練はない
I've got nothing left to live for.
My name is Sato.
（佐藤(さとう)）
私の名前は佐藤　亜人です
I'm an Ajin.
政府は亜人で
非人道的な人体実験を行っている
The government conducts
inhumane experiments on Ajins.
I will start a protest
in front of the Ministry.
私は抗議活動を行います！
場所は厚生労働省前！
（爆発音）
（悲鳴）
（報道陣）
うおっ！
It's today, isn't it?
（下村泉(しもむらいずみ)）
今日… ですね
What are you going to do?
どうするつもりですか？
Nothing's going to change.
（戸崎）
何も変わらんよ
あんなことで人間は動かない
That wasn't enough to get people moving.
This plan wasn't aimed to gather humans.
この作戦は
人間を集めるためのものじゃない
It's to gather Ajins.
亜人を集めるためのものだ
（田中功次(たなかこうじ)ＩＢＭ）
よく来てくれた
これから本当の集合場所を伝える
Thanks for coming.
Now I'll tell you
the real gathering place.
ＦＫは持ってきたんだろうな？
I hope you brought me my cigarettes.
I swore to myself that I would
reach my goal, no matter the cost.
（戸崎）
“どれだけ他人を不幸にしようと
目的を達成する”と
全て出してもらうぞ
あんたが握っているもの 全て
I'll take everything.
Whatever you've got, I want it.
（圭）
はぁっ…
（せきこみ）
I've gotten used to pain...
痛いのは慣れてきたけど
But drowning...
溺れるのは… はぁっ… 苦しいなぁ
...freaking sucks.
ううっ… やっぱ 人助けなんて…
Rescuing people...
ああ… はぁ…
するもんじゃないなぁ
...really isn't worth the effort at all.
ああ… はぁ…
（手をたたく音）
Is this everyone?
（佐藤ＩＢＭ）
これで全員かな？
I'm Sato.
私が佐藤だ
みんな 上がってきてくれ
Come in, everyone.
AJIN: DEMI-HUMAN
深く眠れるかい？
傷は癒せたかい？
Do you sleep well?
Did your wounds heal?
Just cos' they say the night is lonely
夜が寂しいからって
無理して
誰かを愛さないで
You don't have to force yourself
To love someone
They say I'm dreaming
夢を見る事だって
咽び泣く事だって
They say I'm sobbing
They say I tried to die without knowing
知りもしないまま
死んでみたって
上手に隠れたかい？
息は潜めたかい？
Did you manage to hide?
Did you hold your breath?
今が苦しいからって
Just cos' they say it's tough now
You don't have to force yourself to change
無理して自分を変えないで
Even a brave savage
勇敢な蛮人だって
悩める子羊だって
Even a troubled lamb
They are just wandering through life
回り道して生きているって
目立たないように
So I don't stand out
堪えられるように
So I can put up with it
So my train of thought won't stop yet
思考回路はまだ
止めないように
Tonight run away, run a way
It's unbelievable
今宵 RUN AWAY  RUN A WAY
嘘みたいだ
Someone take my hand
誰かこの手
掴んでくれよ
The tomorrow we can't see
Doesn't have to come
見えない明日は来なくていい
今はただ 眠りたい
Now I just want to sleep
BRACE YOURSELVES
（圭）
はぁ… はぁ…
（山中(やまなか)）ああっ！
（ブレーキ音）
（圭）
おおっ！
（山中）
ああっ！
ああ… ううっ…
Why did you jump out like that...?
何だい！
いきなり飛び出してきて
This is bad...
（圭）
まずい…
（山中）
ああ… いたたたた… ああ…
（うめき声）
It's not my fault she fell...
I should just leave her.
勝手に転ぶ方が悪いんだ
放っとけばいい
（山中）
あぁ… いたたた…
ああ ふぅ ああ…
（圭）
あーっ もう！
Ah, damn it!
（うめき声）
My, what a sight.
絶景だね
This is probably the first time...
君たちも初めてだろう
...any of you have seen
so many Ajins in one place.
これだけの亜人が集まる光景は
（男性）
あの… 佐藤さん
Mr. Sato.
We're not exactly on board with this yet.
僕は
まだ 仲間というわけじゃない
（佐藤）
ん？
あなたが 亜人の権利を
どう訴えていくのか―
First of all, I'd like to hear your plan,
as to how
you're going to work for Ajin rights.
そのプランを説明していただきたい
（ゲン）
そうだね　それ知りたい
Yeah, he's right...
We all wanna know that.
うーん…
I don't have anything
as elaborate as a plan.
プランなんて
そんな大層なものはないよ
I'll just do my best at whatever I can.
出来る限りのことを精一杯やるんだ
（高橋(たかはし)）
もっと具体的に言ってもらいてぇな
We'd like you to be
more specific than that.
All right, a massacre.
大量虐殺だよ
（どよめき）
（ゲン）フッ
（高橋）ハハハ…
I gave them an extension
with that broadcast...
あの放送で猶予は与えた
Government cover-ups...
apathetic citizens...
事実を隠蔽(いんぺい)する政府 無関心な国民
I'm not going to let them
get away with it anymore.
私は もう容赦する気がない
Yeah, but...
There are only a few of us here.
…つっても しょせんは
この人数だぜ？
Is there really a chance of success?
勝算は あんのかよ？
Of course... I'm up for it.
やるよ 私は
（ゲン）ククク…
（高橋）ヒュー
Are you idiots?!
（消防士）
馬鹿か！
そんなこと すべきじゃない！
You can't actually be serious!
もちろん 全員から
賛同を得ようなんて思ってないよ
Naturally... I didn't expect that
all of you would agree with me.
So, then who... disagrees with me?
えーと 反対派は？
This one here... and those two?
君と… そっちの２人
Oh... and you?
あれ？ 君は？
（中野攻(なかのこう)）
えっ ああ…
What do you think?
（佐藤）
君は どうする？
Um, I'm against it.
反対… です
Oh, okay then...
ああ そうか　残念だな
That's too bad...
Well, in that case, those who disagree
are free to go.
じゃあ 反対派は
帰ってもらって構わないよ
Come on, let's go.
行きましょう
Sato...
（消防士）
佐藤…
ふざけたことは させないぞ！
I won't let you do anything stupid...!
I swear that I'll stop you.
必ず やめさせる
フフフ…
ん？　あっ！
（蹴る音）
（消防士）うわっ！
（銃声）
（男性）あっ！
Are you okay?!
大丈夫か！？
Run!
（消防士）逃げろ！
（銃声）
（男性）
ああっ！ ぐっ！
ええいっ！
はぁっ はぁっ
EMERGENCY EXIT
あっ こっちだ　走れ！
That way! Run!
Are we just gonna leave
the others in there?!
（攻）
他のやつら 置いてくのかよ！？
If we get caught here...
who's going to stop Sato?!
（消防士）
ここで捕まったら
誰が佐藤を止める？
（田中）
あら？　開かねぇ
It won't open.
What should we do, Mr. Sato?
（田中）
どうします？　佐藤さん
あっ…
（佐藤）
はぁ… 君は本当に
射撃がうまくならないなぁ
Your aim...
...sure hasn't gotten any better...
You hit me.
うっ… 当たったよ
I'm gonna die.
死んじゃうよ
す… すんません
I'm sorry.
But you landed a good shot on this one.
でも 彼の命中箇所はグッドだね
（男性のうめき声）
What do we do... with these guys?
（田中）
こいつら どうします？
Stuff them in some barrels...
and lock them in the basement.
ドラム缶に閉じ込めて
地下にでも監禁しておこう
（消防士）
はぁっ はぁっ…
分かったろ　あれがやつの本性だ
But now you saw his true colors!
What about the others...?
残ってた連中は？
My guess is... He'll keep them captive.
恐らく監禁だろうな
くっ！
Now...
よーし
Let's see just how committed
you guys really are!
君たちのやる気を見せてもらおう
You'll be Tanaka's assistants.
君たちは田中君の補佐だ
逃げたやつらを追って
動きを封じてもらう
Chase down the guys who ran away,
and bring them back.
（高橋）
フッフフフ… ヒュー
And you...
（佐藤）
もう１人は…
I'm unable to run.
（奥山(おくやま)）
僕は走れないよ
I was born with a weak right leg.
生まれつき 右足の筋肉が弱いんだ
Even when I die and come back,
my leg is still the same.
死んで生き返っても
足は このままだった
So how can you contribute?
（佐藤）
どう貢献できる？
That.
（奥山）
それ…
（田中）
ああ？
That rifle has a slightly bent barrel, so
you should aim a little bit to the left.
そのダートライフル
銃身が少し曲がってるから―
ちょっと 左を狙った方がいい
And the CO2 cartridge is a little loose.
あと ＣＯ２ボンベの締めが弱いよ
（田中）
んん…
Guess I know a little more about guns
and machines than Mr. Tanaka.
銃とか機械なら
田中さんより詳しいみたいだけど
Very good.
いいね　悪くないよ
Not bad at all.
さあ ゲーム開始だ！
So, the game begins!
There's a way out!
（消防士）
出口だ！
（攻）
外に出たら どうする？
What'll we do when we get outside?
ぐぐ… ああ くそ！
You go back to your normal life!
お前は普通の生活をしてろ
This is no job for a kid!
ガキの仕事じゃない！
（攻）わあっ！
（消防士）うあっ！
-Damn it.
-What do we do?
くそっ！
どうするよ？
（ドアが開く音）
Over there!
（田中）
こっちだ！
Jump!
（消防士）
飛び降りろ！　俺が時間稼ぎをする
I'll buy some time!
（攻）
えっ？　こ… ここから！？
From here?
亜人だろ！　さっさと飛び降りろ！
You're an Ajin, aren't you?
Now hurry up and jump!
I'm afraid of heights.
高所恐怖症なんだけど…
Listen, those guys won't quit.
いいか？　やつらは死ぬことがない
Even if the police get in their way,
たとえ警察に妨害されようが―
there's no telling how many people
they're going to kill!
無差別に大勢の人間を
殺すことが出来る！
んなこと言われても…
Yeah, but...
I have a family.
俺には家族が… 娘がいる
A daughter.
No matter what happens,
I have to stop those guys!
何が何でも
やつを止めなきゃならない！
だ… だったら押してくれよ！
Okay, then push me!
ん！？　ガキを突き落とせるか！
I can't push a kid out a window!
（銃声）
（消防士）うわっ！
Mister!
おっさん！
（高橋）
当たったぞ
We got him!
Mr. Tanaka! Now!
田中さん！　今だ！
（銃声）
うあっ！
You really are bad at that.
ホントに下手だな
Shut up...!
黙れ！
ぐ… くっ もう お前しかいない
Now, it's up to you.
（攻）
はぁ！？
You're the only one...
お前しか佐藤を止められない！
...who can stop Sato now!
Wait a mi--
（攻）
ちょ… ちょっと待っ…
You have to stop him!
絶対に やつを止めろ…　行け！
Now go!
（攻）
わ… 分かった！
Okay!
A little to the left.
（田中）
少し左…
（銃声）
だっ…
Mister!
（攻）
おっさん！
何！？
What?
（攻）
ああっ… わっ
Hurry!
（消防士）
は… 早く… 行け！　ぐっ…
Go!
あ… ああ…
Right...
マジかよっ！
You gotta be kidding!
This is the TV footage taken
in front of the ministry the other day.
（曽我部(そかべ)）
これは先日 省前で撮られた
テレビカメラの映像です
この男 見えない何かが
ぶつかったように―
This man staggers unnaturally here,
as though he bumped into
something we can't see.
不自然に よろめいてます
うーん　ＩＢＭがいたのか
So there was an IBM there.
Yes, although unfortunately
we can't tell how many.
（曽我部）
ええ 残念ながら
数までは分かりませんが
Zoom in there.
ズームしてくれ
There's really nothing else to see.
これ以上見ても何もありませんよ
違う　この奥の男だ
No, that one back there.
He's following something with his eyes...
何かを目で追うような動作…
横切るＩＢＭが見えてる
He can see the IBM walk by.
He's the one...
手掛かりは この男だ
He's our lead.
はぁっ… はぁっ… はぁっ…
がっ… はぁっ… はぁっ…
（田中）
ちっ 逃げ足の速い野郎だな
The little bastard sure can run.
Hey.
（消防士）
おい…
Do you really think that...
佐藤のやり方なんかで…
いいと思ってるのか？
...what Sato's doing is right?
What's that?
何だと？
The reason the government
hides information on the Ajins...
政府が亜人の情報を
隠蔽するのは―
...is probably just to avoid panic.
き… きっと
パニックを避けたいだけだ
だが
テロのようなことをすれば―
But if...
...you start with this terrorism...
...things will get out of hand.
とんでもないことになるぞ…
The whole country will support...
hunting down Ajin.
全国民同意の―
亜人狩りが始まる…
う…
Are you sure that it's okay?
本当に いいんですか？
お世話になっちゃって…
Letting me stay here?
It's fine.
（山中）
いいのよ
After all, you carried me here,
and brought my things in too.
おぶってもらったうえに
荷物まで運んでもらったんだし
あ… どうもすいません
Thank you so much.
She already saw my face anyway...
どうせ 顔を見られたんだし
下手に逃げ出すよりは…
This is less suspicious
than running away...
Here you are.
（山中）
お待たせ
こんなものしかなくて悪いけど
Sorry I don't have anything else to offer.
And now for our next story.
（テレビ音声：キャスター）
次のニュースです
３日前 研究所から逃走した亜人
永井圭の捜索は…
The search for Kei Nagai continues,
an Ajin who escaped from
the research facility three days ago.
うっ…
The police have increased their forces,
and are asking for eyewitness accounts.
（キャスター）
警察は捜査員を増員すると共に
広く目撃情報を呼び掛けています
There has been a great deal of uproar
about Ajins lately...
人体実験疑惑や謎の爆発事件など
世間を騒がせている亜人問題ですが
...with doubts about human experimentation
and mysterious explosions.
今後 どのような展開を
見せるのでしょうか
What does the future hold?
I don't plan on doing anything rash...
余計なことをするつもりはないよ
I'm sure every man
has his own reasons, anyway.
男にゃ いろんな事情が
あるだろうしね
え…
So you're called Kei?
（山中）
圭君… だっけ？
I have a grandson
about the same age as you.
私にも同じぐらいの孫がいんのよ
His name's Ryota,
but I haven't seen him in years...
良太(りょうた)っていうんだけど
もう何年も会ってなくてねぇ
ふぅ… はぁ…
This is perfect for testing a few things.
いろいろと試すには
うってつけだな
はぁ…
Sato?
あっ 佐藤！
あ？
It's not him.
別人じゃねぇか
はぁ… はぁ…
あっ
Is that an Ajin?
あれは亜人の！？
No.
いや あれは
佐藤がいた方向じゃない
That's not the direction Sato was.
あ… じゃ 誰なんだ？
Then...
...who is it?
ああ… もう また消えた
なんで勝手に消えるんだよ
It's gone already...
Why does it disappear on its own?
（ため息）
But...
でも
もう あれの出し方は分かった
...at least now I know how to summon it.
（圭ＩＢＭ）
やっぱ 人助けなんて
するもんじゃないなぁ
Rescuing people... really...
isn't worth... all the effort.
This is the fifth one.
（圭）
これで５体目　だいぶ
連続して出せるようになったな
I can summon it several times
in a row now.
はぁ…
はぁ… あぁ…
うわっ！
Oh, good morning.
（女性）
あら おはよう
（攻）
ああ ハハ…
お… おはようございます
Good morning.
（女性）
ああっ… やだ！　すごい血！
Oh, my! So much blood!
え… ああ これ？
ちょっと転んじゃって…
Oh, this? I just had a little fall...
（女性）
救急車！
救急車 呼んだほうがいいわよ！
Ambulance!
You need to call an ambulance!
そんな 大丈夫だって へへへ…
Oh, no. I'm fine.
あのおばさん
ホント おせっかいだよなぁ…
That old lady's so nosy...
（ため息）
（鍵を回す音）
（攻）あ？
鍵 開けっ放しだったか
I must have left it unlocked.
え？
You're Ko Nakano, right?
（男性）
中野攻君だね？　ここに住んでる
This is your place?
そう… だけど…
Yes... But, uh...
（銃声）
（攻）あっ ぐっ…
（男性）くそっ！
（平沢(ひらさわ)）逃がすな！
-Damn it!
-Don't let him get away!
Those guys in black...
（泉）
あの黒服たちってオグラ博士の所に
いた人たちですよね？
...are the same ones
who were with Dr. Ogura, right...?
Yeah.
ああ
厚労省の人たちですか？
-Are they from the Ministry?
-Of course not...
そんなわけないだろう
They were employed by a certain man.
（戸崎）
ある男が雇っていた連中だ
And then I recruited them back again...
それを私が再び招集した
They've proven themselves quite useful.
さまざまな仕事をしてくれる
少々 荒っぽいこともな
They don't mind getting their hands dirty.
はぁっ はぁっ はぁっ…
ああっ！
ああっ… くっ…
く… くそっ また飛び降りかよ！
Damn, I've gotta jump again?!
だっ！　ああっ？
That's far enough.
（男性）
そこまでだ
なっ…
Damn, damn, damn!
やばい やばい やばい！
（銃声）
（攻）うっ！
（攻）
んんっ… うおおっ！
（男性）
おおっ！
（攻）
どわっ…
（悲鳴）
があっ！ ううっ…
（うめき声）
（せきこみ）
You're the only one...
お前しか佐藤を止められない！
...who can stop Sato now!
わ… 分かってるよ…
Yeah, I know...
Goddamn it.
くっそぉ…
-What do we do?
-Run him over.
（泉）どうします？
（戸崎）はねろ
（泉）
え？
I'll do it if you won't.
嫌なら代われ
（攻）
はぁっ はぁっ…
はっ！？
（攻）
あ… あ…
はぁっ… ああ… くっ…
はっ
（救急車のサイレン）
なっ！？　くっ…
あ… あれ？
（ドアの開く音）
We were told
there was an injured man here!
（救急隊員）
“ケガをした男性がいる”と通報が
We didn't know it was this serious...!
（救急隊員）
こんなに重傷とは！
あ…
You said you were told...?
通報って…
（サイレン）
ハ… ハハ ハハハ…
（救急隊員）
わ… 笑ってるぞ…
He's laughing?
He may have a head injury.
（救急隊員）
頭を強く打ったのかもしれん
ハッ…
（平沢たち）
はぁっ はぁっ はぁっ…
-Sorry, sir.
-Find out exactly where he's being taken.
（平沢）
すみません
どこに運ばれるか調べろ
With injuries like that,
they must be going to a hospital.
あのケガなら
恐らくは入院になるはずだ
（心電計のアラーム）
（救急隊員）
はぁ…　バイタル停止
間に合いませんでした
His vitals have stopped...
We were too late...
Damn it... He must have
lost too much blood.
（救急隊員）
くそ　出血が多すぎたか
They're already expecting us.
もう 受け入れ準備も
してもらってます
Anyway, let's carry him in...
とにかく運びましょう
があっ！　はぁっ！
ああ？
はぁっ はぁっ はぁっ…
Damn it.
くそ！　誰にも知られてないのが
俺の強みだったのに！
The fact that no one knew about me
was my one advantage!
ん？
That...
あれは…
...was an Ajin,
but not one of those guys with Sato...
佐藤たちとは別の亜人？
I can keep it out longer
than yesterday, but...
昨日より長い時間
出せるようになったけど…
Why does it... disappear... on its own...
（圭ＩＢＭ）
なんで 勝手に消え …るんだよ
それは こっちのセリフだし
That's what I want to know.
How's it going, Okuyama?
（佐藤）
どうだい？　奥山君
Oh, I'm already finished.
（奥山）
ああ もう出来てるよ
I'm borrowing a residential line.
回線は一般人の家から拝借
The upload is going
through Russian and Chinese servers,
アップロードはロシアや中国の
サーバーを経由してるし―
so it won't be traced.
バレることはないね
（佐藤）
ああ…
Nice, very nice.
いいね　いい感じだ
It's looking good.
Thanks.
どうも
Hi, we meet again.
やあ また会ったね　亜人の佐藤だ
This is Sato the Ajin.
But I have to tell you
something important today.
今日 話すのは楽しい話じゃない
I'll make it brief...
切迫… 我々は追い詰められた
We are now being hunted down...
Therefore, I've had to make
a difficult decision...
だから 決断せざるを得なかった
And that is...
我々は 武力によって
住みよい国造りをスタートさせる
We're going to create a country
we can live in, through force.
The first wave will be on Wednesday
ten days from now, at 3 p.m.
第１ウエーブは
10日後の水曜 午後３時
We will attack
Grant Pharmaceuticals headquarters.
グラント製薬の本社を襲撃する
For the sake of all the Ajin
still wondering whether or not to fight,
まだ 参戦を迷っている
亜人のためにも―
圧倒的な戦闘力を披露しよう
we will demonstrate our true strength.
And to the humans who think
this doesn't involve you...
無関係だと思っている人間たち
...everything is just about to begin.
いよいよ始まるぞ
So brace yourselves.
衝戟(しょうげき)に備えろ
TO BE CONTINUED
If my wish would come true
願い叶(かな)うなら
もう一度
Once again
君の心に
触れていたい
I wanna touch your heart
No matter how dark it gets
どんな闇でも
探してるんだ
I'll be searching
For my one
たったひとつの
光を
And only light
As I look up to the stars
遠いけど
Even though you are far
同じ星空　見上げてる
You're looking up at the same starry sky
心の空には
雫(こぼ)れ落ちそうな
In the sky of my heart
It's about to spill over
Your smile and
君の笑顔と
ぬくもり
Your warmth
Hear me
Until I went away and
Faced the lonely days
愛することの意味なんて
I thought I could understand
分かってたつもりだった
What it means to love
Feeling everything that
Was right in front of me
大切なもの失って
Losing something precious
本当の愛に気付いて
Realizing real love
I'll tell you now
I'll tell you now,
Just how close you are